<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss xmlns:a10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"> <channel xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" <item><title>Hotifx 1.2005.29.100</title><description><ul><li>Added PEP to retrieve current registration details, stale object cleanup for Remove-Registration.</li><li>Improved reliability of log collection for SDN roles by collecting on file share.</li></ul></description><link>https://review.docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure-stack/operator/hotfix-1-2005-29-100?view=azs-1802&branch=pr-en-us-6474</link><release>2005</release><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>2021-02-05</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://azurestackhubdocs.azurewebsites.net/xml/hotfix.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /></item><item><title>Hotifx 1.2008.25.114</title><description><ul><li>Fixed issue in internal secret rotation that would fail with a timeout error if value-add resource providers were unhealthy.</li> <li>Fixed a bug in which closed alerts' Last Modified Time was updated in the operator portal even if the alert stayed closed.</li> <li>Optimized operator alert request handling, which reduces the chance of timeouts when viewing alerts in the operator portal or monitoring them via SCOM.</li> <li>Check and enforce key protectors on cluster shared volumes per host.</li> <li>Fixed issue in which Managed Disk usage data was not being reported after the 2008 update.</li> <li>Fixed VMs losing connectivity while SuspendNode is occurring in MAS, as part of host reboot during patch and update.</li> <li>Added PEP to retrieve current registration details, stale object cleanup for Remove-Registration.</li> <li>Fixed a bug which caused the Infrastructure Roles panel in the operator portal to display incorrect health information.</li> <li>Improved reliability of log collection for SDN roles by collecting logs on the file share.</li></ul></description><link>https://review.docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure-stack/operator/hotfix-1-2008-25-114?view=azs-1802</link><release>2008</release><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>2021-02-05</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://azurestackhubdocs.azurewebsites.net/xml/hotfix.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /></item></channel></rss>